mihomes.com 2006-10-14

# M/I Homes - mihomes.com Privacy Statement

|  |   
---|---  
|  |   
---  

|   
---  
|  | 

**_Privacy Statement_**  
  
---  
  
   M/I Homes, Inc., and its subsidiaries ("M/I") value your customer satisfaction. This privacy statement is intended to assist you in understanding what information M/I gathers about you, how M/I uses that information, and the safeguards M/I has in place for the information.   
  
   M/I collects personal information which you may voluntarily provide through our contact forms on the mihomes.com website, as well as information you may provide at our sales centers, models, on referral websites, or when you participate in a survey for M/I. The information collected may include your name, e-mail address, phone number, as well as other information which can identify you personally.   
  
   M/I collects this information in order to be responsive to the needs and requests of prospective customers. By collecting such information, M/I is better suited to provide a system by which pertinent information on the products and services M/I offers is made available to customers. M/I may use your personal information in order to contact you via telephone, e-mail, e-newsletter, or regular mail for the express business purpose of providing information as M/I may deem appropriate regarding promotions, new communities, or other items of interest.   
  
   M/I is the sole owner of any information you may voluntarily provide and will not sell or lease any information you may provide to any third party companies or individuals. M/I may, however, share information that you provide with third party service providers that assist M/I in such things as conducting surveys, maintaining our database, administering our web site or sending and administering e-mails, or other similar services. Only that information necessary to provide these services is shared with third party service providers. Additionally, there may be circumstances under which M/I may be required, by law or order, to provide information it has collected, or M/I may make information available to certain authorized parties when necessary, and as appropriate, in order to protect M/I's proprietary interests from harm due to fraud or other illegal activities.   
  
   M/I reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Statement at any time and for any reason in order to maintain compliance with applicable laws or to reflect or update changes in M/I's business practices. You may revoke your authorization to receive eNewsletters from M/I by following the unsubscription instructions in the eNewsletter.   
  
   You may revoke your authorization to receive eNewsletters from M/I by following the unsubscription instructions in the eNewsletter.   
  
   This document was last revised on 10/27/2005.  
© Copyright 2005, M/I Homes, Inc. All rights reserved.
